I can't help but stress this to people,
but for many years, absolutely nothing
happened within my business. So 2014,
2015,
2016, there was no growth.
If you'd met me back in the day,
and you'd sat
next to me in Waitrose and you'd said,
"Hey, mate.
What are you doing?" I'd say, "Yeah,
I post on social media every single day."
"Oh,
you got any clients from it?" "No." "Has
it benefited your business?" "No." You
would've thought I was mental for so long,
and it took me three years of posting
every day on social media for things to,
quote unquote, take off.
And the very last one
is just showing you my Instagram
when it had 14,000
followers. Don't know if the autofocus
is going to get that.
But there was a time that, just like you,
I had a small account, and when I got
to 14,000, I thought I'd made it. I
was like, "Oh my God.
This is god tier.
How am I going to move in the street
without people going, 'Oh,
there's that personal trainer from Fitness
First?'" So straight off the bat, you
don't need to have a big account.
You don't need to have any crazy
following, crazy technical setup,
any of those things.
You just need to have a good attitude